<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<spring_table>
    <string id="ui_mcm_menu_ym_smart_music_mute">
        <text>Smart Music Mute</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_base_desc"> 
        <text>How It Works:
        \n\n When you first crouch, the mod will decrease the music volume by the Initial Volume Drop, then decrease by the Rate of Change until the music is 0.
        \n During this, if you don't stand up yet, a timer will count up behind the scenes. The longer you are crouched, the more time it acrues. 
        \n When you stand back up, this time will start counting back down; the music volume will not start to turn back up until the timer reaches 0.
        The idea being that, if you are crouched for a long period of time, you are trying to be sneaky, and want the music to stay silent, even if you stand back up to get into a firefight.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_key_bind_toggle">
        <text>Mute Music</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_key_bind_toggle_desc">
        <text>Toggle the in-game music.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_initial_vol_dampen">
        <text>Initial Volume Drop</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_initial_vol_dampen_desc">
        <text>When you first crouch, lower volume by this percentage amount.
        \n\nSetting to 1 will make volume mute as soon as you crouch.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_rate_of_change">
        <text>Rate of Change</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_rate_of_change_desc">
        <text>Amount of volume per second that the volume with decrease.
            \n\n%c[d_green]--%c[DEFAULT] Maximum volume is 1.0, and the minimum is 0.0
            \n\n%c[d_green]--%c[DEFAULT] From volume 1.0, if you set the rate of change to 0.1, it will take 10 seconds to decrease the volume to 0.0
            \n\n%c[d_red]--%c[DEFAULT] If you set it to 1, music will mute as soon as you crouch
            \n\n%c[d_red]--%c[DEFAULT] If you set it to 0, the rate of change will be disabled. %c[d_red]Only the Initial Volume Drop will affect the volume after that. 
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_combat_mute">
        <text>Combat Mute</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ym_smart_music_mute_combat_mute_desc">
        <text>Mute music upon entering combat.</text>
    </string>
</spring_table>